curiosityhuman.com 2016-11-18

# Privacy Policy

[vc_row][vc_column][vc_column_text]Privacy Policy:

CH Team operates curiosityhuman.com and may operate other websites. It is CH’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

CuriosityHuman Visitors

Like most website operators, CH collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. CH’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how CH’s visitors use its website. From time to time, CH may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

CH also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on curiosityhuman.com blogs/sites. CH only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, except that commenter IP addresses and email addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog/site where the comment was left.

Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. CH uses cookies to help CH identify and track visitors, their usage of CH website, and their website access preferences. CH visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using CH’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of CH’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

Ads

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by CH and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, CH may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in CH’s sole discretion. CH encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have a curiosityhuman.com account, you might also receive an alert informing you of these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

Attribution

The information that we received from <https://automattic.com/privacy/> to make privacy policy for CH, It is licensed under a <http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/>

Contact us

Any further queries and questions regarding policy please feel free to send us – http://curiosityhuman.com/contact-us/

[/vc_column_text][/vc_column][/vc_row]
